<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Eritrea Tour Guider</string>
    <string name="city">Cities</string>
    <string name="hotel">Hotels</string>
    <string name="ethnics">Ethnics</string>
    <string name="legacy">Legacy</string>
    <string name="asmara">Asmara</string>
    <string name="desc_asmara">Asmara is the capital city of Eritrea, a country in the Horn of Africa. It\'s known for its Italian colonial buildings, like the Catholic Cathedral. The city\'s eclectic architecture ranges from art deco cinemas to the Futurist, airplane-shaped Fiat Tagliero service station. The grand former governor\'s palace dates from the 19th century. Close by is the ornate Opera House, built in the early 1900s in a mix of styles.</string>
    <string name="massawa">Massawa</string>
    <string name="desc_massawa">Massawa is a port city in Eritrea, on Africa\'s Red Sea coast. In the old town, on Massawa Island, a mix of Italian, Egyptian and Ottoman architecture reflects the city\'s colorful history. On nearby Taulud Island, notable buildings include the crumbling, war-damaged Imperial Palace and St. Mariam Cathedral. Near the cathedral, 3 tanks form a monument commemorating those who died in Eritrea\'s civil wars.</string>
    <string name="keren">Keren</string>
    <string name="desc_keren">Keren, also spelled Cheren, and historically known as Sanhit, is the second-largest city in Eritrea. It is situated around 91 kilometres northwest of Asmara at an elevation of 1,390 metres above sea-level. The city sprawls on a wide basin surrounded by granitic mountains on all sides.</string>
    <string name="adi_keyh">Adi Keyh</string>
    <string name="desc_adi_keyh">Adi Keyh is a market town in Eritrea, lying approximatively 110 kilometers southeast of Asmara. It lies almost 2,500 metres above sea level and has a population of around 40,000 people. They speak Tigrinya and saho. The ruins of Qohaito and Toconda lie near the town.</string>
    <string name="dekemhare">Dekemhare</string>
    <string name="desc_dekemhare">Dekemhare is a town in Eritrea, lying south east of Asmara. Developed by the Italians as an industrial center, it became a large scale industrial and transportation city, known for its vineyards but was largely destroyed in the Eritrean War of Independence.</string>
    <string name="segheneyti">Segheneyti</string>
    <string name="desc_segheneyti">Segheneytī is a small town in the Southern Region of Eritrea. The town lies on the road between Asmara and Senafe. Saho, Tigre and Tigrigna ethnic groups live in it. Islam and christianity are predominant.</string>
    <string name="ghinda">Gīnda</string>
    <string name="desc_ghinda">Ghinda is a town in the Northern Red Sea region of Eritrea. It is situated in the Ghinda Subregion, and lies between Asmara and Massawa.Ghinda is a major fruit and vegetable growing area and a centre for Tigre Muslims. It lies near the springs of Sabarguma. The citrus plantations were originally planted by Carlo Cavanna, an Italian from Centenaro who directed the construction of the Eritrean Railway, the first railway in Italian Eritrea.</string>
    <string name="assab">Āssab</string>
    <string name="desc_assab">Assab or Aseb is a port city in the Southern Red Sea Region of Eritrea. It is situated on the west coast of the Red Sea. Languages spoken in Assab are predominantly Afar, Tigrinya, and Arabic.n 1989, Assab had a population of 39,600 inhabitants. It possessed an oil refinery, which was shut down in 1997 for economic reasons. Until 1998, Ethiopia used Assab as port to process 2/3rd of its trade with the world. Ever since and due to closed borders between Eritrea and Ethiopia, both the port and the port town lost most of their relevance.</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone:</string>
    <string name="kunama">Kunama people</string>
    <string name="desc_kunama">The Kunama are a Nilotic ethnic group inhabiting Eritrea and Ethiopia. Although they are one of the smallest populations in Eritrea, constituting only 2% of the population, 80% of Kunama live in the country.</string>
    <string name="afar">Afar people</string>
    <string name="desc_afar">The Afar, also known as the Danakil, Adali and Odali, are an ethnic Cushitic people inhabiting the Horn of Africa. They primarily live in the Afar Region of Ethiopia and in northern Djibouti, although some also inhabit the southern point of Eritrea.</string>
    <string name="saho">Saho people</string>
    <string name="desc_saho">The Saho are an ethnic Cushitic peoples inhabiting the Horn of Africa. They are principally concentrated in Eritrea, with some also living in adjacent parts of Ethiopia. They speak Saho as a mother tongue, which belongs to the Cushitic branch of the Afroasiatic family and is closely related to Afar.</string>
    <string name="rashaida">Rashaida people</string>
    <string name="desc_rashaida">The Rashaida, Rashaayda or Bani Rashid is a tribe of ethnic Bedouin Arabs descending from Banu Abs native to the Hejaz region of Saudi Arabia. They currently inhabit Saudi Arabia, Kuwait, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain, Oman, Yemen, Palestine, Jordan, Eritrea, Sudan, Libya and Tunisia.</string>
    <string name="zone_kunama">Location: Gash-Barka Region</string>
    <string name="zone_afar">Location: Southern Red Sea Region</string>
    <string name="zone_saho">Location: Southern and Northern Red Sea Region</string>
    <string name="zone_rashaida">Location: Northern Red Sea Region</string>
    <string name="tigrinya">Tigrinya people</string>
    <string name="zone_tigrinya">Location: Central and Southern Region</string>
    <string name="desc_tigrinya">The Tigrayans or Tigrinyas are an ethnolinguistic group indigenous to Northeast Africa who primarily inhabit the highlands of Eritrea and the Tigray Region of Ethiopia. They speak the Tigrinya language, a direct descendant of the Ge’ez language that was spoken in late antiquity.</string>
    <string name="bilen">Bilen people</string>
    <string name="zone_bilen">Location: Anseba and Central Region</string>
    <string name="desc_bilen">The Bilen are a Cushitic ethnic group in the Horn of Africa. They are primarily concentrated in central Eritrea, in and around the city of Keren and further south toward Asmara, the nation\'s capital.</string>
    <string name="nara">Nara people</string>
    <string name="zone_nara">Location: Gash-Barka Region</string>
    <string name="desc_nara">The Nara are an ethnic group inhabiting southwestern Eritrea. The society is divided into four subtribes, who traditionally were animist but now follow Islam. They are mostly subsistence farmers.</string>
    <string name="tigre">Tigre people</string>
    <string name="zone_tigre">Location: Gash-Barka and Anseba Region</string>
    <string name="desc_tigre">The Tigre people are an ethnic group indigenous to Eritrea. They mainly inhabit the lowlands of Eritrea and the Sudanese states of Kassala and Red Sea. They are closely related to the Tigrayans and Beja. The Tigre speak the Tigre language, which belongs to the Semitic branch of the Afroasiatic family.</string>
    <string name="hedareb">Hedareb people</string>
    <string name="zone_hedareb">Location: Gash-Barka Region</string>
    <string name="desc_hedareb">The Hedareb or T\'bdawe are one of the nine ethnolinguistic groups in Eritrea. They are a Beni-Amer division, a subgroup of the Beja. They are more diverse than the other Eritrean ethics; one subgroup speaks the traditional Beja language, which belongs to the Cushitic branch of the Afro-Asiatic family, while another is more closely related to Sudanese Hadendoa.</string>
    <string name="fiat">Fiat Tagliero Building</string>
    <string name="desc_fiat">The Fiat Tagliero Building in Asmara, capital city of Eritrea, is a Futurist-style service station completed in 1938 and designed by the Italian engineer Giuseppe Pettazzi.</string>
    <string name="cathedral">Cathedral in Asmara</string>
    <string name="desc_cathedral">The Church of Our Lady of the Rosary, Asmara is a Roman Catholic church built in early 1920s in Asmara, when was the capital of Italian Eritrea.</string>
    <string name="cinema_impero">Cinema Impero</string>
    <string name="desc_cinema_impero">The Cinema Impero (lit. \"Empire Cinema\") is an Art Deco-style cinema in Asmara, the capital of Eritrea. It was built in 1937 by the colonial authorities in Italian Eritrea.</string>
    <string name="italian_bank">The Former Banca D\'italia</string>
    <string name="desc_italian_bank">The battered former Italian Bank, Banca d\'Italia, next to the main entrance to the Massawa port; Massawa, also known as Mitsiwa or Massaoua is a port city on the Red Sea coast of Eritrea, important for many centuries, it has been colonised by Egypt, the turkish Ottoman Empire, Italy, England and was finally part of Ethiopia until the independence of Eritrea in 1991 after a long war, the old town is still full of old houses, but many are in ruins, as heavy fights took place between eritrean and ethiopian armies; Massawa is the place to reach the Dalhak archipelago</string>
    <string name="dahlak">Dahlak Archipelago</string>
    <string name="desc_dahlak">The Dahlak Archipelago (Arabic: أرخبيل دهلك‎, Ge\'ez: ዳህላክ) is an island group located in the Red Sea near Massawa, Eritrea. It consists of two large and 124 small islands. The pearl fisheries of the archipelago have been famous since Roman times and still produce a substantial number of pearls.</string>
    <string name="asmara_palace">Hotel Asmara Palace</string>
    <string name="desc_asmara_palace">The hotel is designed to meet business and corporate travelers offering wide choice of themed restaurant outlets such as seafood’s, Italian, Arabian and Asian nights. With Hotel Asmara Palace you have everything to make your stay in Eritrea truly special and utterly unforgettable.</string>
    <string name="phone_asmara_palace">Phone: +291 1 153 701</string>
    <string name="albergo">Albergo Italia Asmara</string>
    <string name="desc_albergo">Welcome to Albergo Italia, a nice option for travellers like you. Rooms at Albergo Italia provide air conditioning, and getting online is easy, with free internet access available. In addition, Albergo Italia offers a lounge, which will help make your Asmara trip additionally gratifying.</string>
    <string name="phone_albergo">Phone: +291 1 120 740</string>
    <string name="dahlak_hotel">Dahlak Hotel</string>
    <string name="desc_dahlak_hotel">Dahlak Hotel is located in Massawa, Eritrea. It\'s one of Massawa oldest hotels and having beautiful view of the coastal area.</string>
    <string name="sunshine">Sunshine Hotel</string>
    <string name="desc_sunshine">Sunshine Hotel is the most prestigious hotel in Eritrea. It is located in the heart of Asmara, the capital city. Sunshine that is still being commended frequently for being very serviceable and of course outranking in the overall internal as well as external comely settings of its environment, became functional on July 27, 1996. Yet its doors live across time bearing the spirit of hospitability in the minds of those who tried its service.</string>
    <string name="phone_sunshine">Phone: +291 1 127880</string>
</resources>
